♪
Morning, Carly.
Morning.
Hey, you know what I hate?
Mornings?
Yeah.
That's not your locker.
Then explain this.
I traded it with
Arthur Gradstein.
Why would Arthur want
your locker between
those two big sweaty wrestlers
who fight all the time?
He didn't.
Which is why I gave Arthur
Freddie's locker
and made Freddie take mine.
I'm telling ya,
this is an illegal move!
Yeah? But that's
different from this!
Uh, guys, seriously...
That's the same thing, dipwad!
Dipwad?!
Okay, okay, time out.
Seriously, you guys!
You're crushing my sack lunch!
This violates so many rules.
Stop it, you guys.
It hurts.
Get off! Quit it!
Hey! They're giving away
free meat in the parking lot!
Stop it!
Free meat?
Protein!
Look what they did
to my pudding cup.
Give me your hand.
Carly.
What?
Jake Krandle
and Stephanie Jeffers broke up.
They broke up?!
Hey, is it true?
Yeah!
They broke up last night.
Which means that Jake Krandle
is single
for the first time
since third grade.
Wait. Wait.
Wait a minute!
So we're all gonna lose
our minds
just 'cause one of us
has a tiny chance
to date Jake Krandle?
That answer your question?
And shattered my ear drum.
In five, four, three, two...
♪
♪ I know, you see ♪
♪ Somehow the world
will change for me ♪
♪ And be so wonderful ♪
♪
♪ Live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow
we're gonna get there ♪
♪ And feel so wonderful ♪
♪
♪ It's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you
just how I feel ♪
♪ So wake up the members
of my nation ♪
♪ It's your time to be ♪
♪ There's no chance
unless you take one ♪
♪ And the time to see
the brighter side ♪
♪ Of every situation ♪
♪ Some things are meant to be
so give me your best ♪
♪ And leave the rest to me ♪
♪ Leave it all to me,
leave it all to me ♪
♪ Just leave it all to me ♪♪
It doesn't matter.
Yeah?
It's more than just cool.
It's really cool.
He can't see us.
I know. Shh.
Okay, it's so not like me
to get all crazy
about a hot guy
like Jake Krandle.
But?
But, my God, he's so hot,
I wanna bake cookies on him.
I'd eat those cookies.
If you like him so much,
say hi to him.
What?! You can't just go say
hi to a guy like Jake Krandle.
What if he says hi back?
Then what do I say?
Just say, "I'm sorry I hit you
in the head with an apple."
Why would I ask...
Ow!
Carly did it.
Um, I think you accidentally
threw this at my head.
Yeah...
Apples can be slippery.
Stupid Fuji.
Well, I should get to class.
Wait.
Okay.
You're Carly Shay, right?
Yeah. Yes, I am.
How do you know my name?
From your web show, "iCarly."
You've seen it?
Yeah, you're really good.
It's weird, I kind of feel
like I'm talking to a celebrity.
That's weird, 'cause I kinda
feel like I'm gonna throw up.
For real?
No, no, it's fine.
I meant throwing up
in the good way.
Oh.
Right, right.
So, we should hang out sometime.
Something wrong?
No, I just swallowed my gum.
But, yeah, we should
totally hang out.
You could come by my house
and I'll show you where
we shoot the show.
Oh, you shoot it at your house?
Well, apartment.
Or I guess it's more of a loft.
It has an elevator.
You're really funny.
Yeah, well.
I'll see you around.
Yes, you will.
What did he say?
Tell me everything.
He said we should
hang out sometime!
Actually, I feel that teachers
should give us more homework.
More homework
and more discipline.
Yes.
Discipline is very important.
I think it's a priority
in school...
♪
So, that's supposed
to be your body?
Well, yeah.
You know, if I looked like this.
It's like you're twins.
So why no head?
That goes on later.
Okay, you ready
to splatter paint?
Okay.
And... Wait.
We need music.
Yeah, we do.
♪
Okay, ready? On three.
One... I can't wait!
Like this?
Yes!
You are the splatter master.
Cool!
Try closing your eyes.
Incoming!
Yes! Feel the music.
Be the paint.
How can I be the paint?
Paint doesn't ask questions.
Good technique.
I got it.
Okay.
Oh, hi, Jake.
Jake!
Hey, I was
in the neighborhood...
Wait here!
Listen, if this is...
What's going on?
I have to make
myself attractive!
How's it going?
Why are you here?
Oh, I just stopped by
to see Carly.
Okay.
There. You've seen her.
Now why don't you just
scurry on out of here?
Hey, sorry about that.
No worries.
It's okay, Carly.
I got the situation
under control.
I was just asking Jake...
Come in, Jake.
I don't think it's a good idea
to be letting this guy in...
You're the best.
Yeah, just keep kissing
those frogs, Carly.
This prince can wait.
So, your older brother
is actually shaped like that?
No, no.
He has a head.
Hey, look, I found hot pink
and orphan blue.
The saddest of all blues.
Yeah, Spencer,
this is my friend Jake.
Jake, this is my brother,
Spencer.
Oh, how's it going... oh,
I probably shouldn't...
Yeah, don't.
I'm gonna take Jake upstairs
and show him
where we shoot iCarly.
You two going up there alone?
Spencer.
Okay.
But, remember,
I could pop up there
at any moment,
like a ninja!
Oh.
Uh, here, let me get you a rag.
And as far away from him
as possible.
A ninja!
♪
And the third floor.
Nice.
It's weird, this room looks
so much bigger on the Internet.
Yeah, the Internet
can distort room size.
Hey, Sam's remote.
Wow, you really do watch iCarly.
Yeah, this controls
all the sound effects, right?
That's it.
Oh, do it, you know you want to.
♪
Sweet.
Hey, what was the name
of that song?
Was it, uh, "Brake Lights"
by Cuddlefish?
Impressive, I didn't think
anybody knew that song.
I do, that was one
of the first songs...
Sorry.
What were you saying?
Just that that was one
of the first songs
I taught myself to play.
You play guitar?
And sing a little.
Really? 'Cause Sam and I
have been talking about
maybe having live music
on the show.
Would you wanna do a song?
Definitely.
Wait, let's check and make sure
your audience is into it.
Well, looks like
I'm singing on iCarly.
Ah, it fell.
I like it better on the floor.
♪
Hello? Carly?
Is that you?
Nah, Carly's upstairs getting...
ready for the show.
What are you doing?
Making a plaster cast
of my head to put on top
of my body sculpture.
Of course you are.
What are the tubes for?
Well, since I'm gonna be
in here for 12 hours
while the plaster dries,
this tube is for breathing,
and this tube
is for food and drink.
Nice.
Well, I'm gonna leave now.
Wait! Before you go,
would you mind pouring some
coffee down my drink hole?
Sure, what are...
friends for?
Okay!
That was my breathing tube!
♪
So. You're tall,
you're an athlete,
every girl in school
thinks you're hot,
and now you're a musician, too.
I guess.
Can you fly?!
Actually, my uncle's a pilot,
he's been giving me
flying lessons...
Oh, forget it!
I'll be with my tripod.
Do you know how many kids
came up to me
freaking out that Jake's
gonna play on the show?
I know, it's gonna be huge.
What?
Would you have ever believed
that Jake Krandle
could be in love with you?
He's not in love with me.
Yet.
Cinnamon buns.
Why do that?
I'm checking the microphone
and the acoustic resonance in...
Whoops! Don't care.
So, what time
does the show start?
In about a half hour.
But, listen,
since we've never done
live music on the show before,
Freddie wants to do
a sound check.
So, you mind running
through a verse?
Let's go for it.
All right, this is a song
I wrote myself
especially for iCarly.
Hope you guys like it.
♪
♪ You're so beautiful ♪
♪ I need the world to see ♪
♪
♪ You're my miracle ♪
♪ Just take the time
that you need ♪
♪ To breathe ♪
How was that?
Awesome.
I can't wait 'til we go live.
♪
Freddie, did you get
a good sound level
or do you want me to sing
another verse?
No, no!
Please don't!
Yeah, we go live
in about 20 minutes.
So maybe you should go
downstairs and get changed.
Right, I gotta go
put on my singing shirt.
Yeah. Put that on.
Yeah, your singing shirt.
Definitely.
You go do that.
Later.
♪ You're so beautiful ♪
Well, I think we know
the results of the sound check.
Did it sound horrible?
Check.
You guys, this isn't funny.
Did you not hear him?
'Cause it was pretty funny.
Stop it.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna tell him
he can't sing on the show
'cause he sounds
like a pile of poo.
I can't just...
I can't just tell him
he's too poo-ish
to sing on our show.
Carly.
I like him,
and I think he kind of likes me.
And if I tell him
he's a terrible singer,
it's gonna ruin everything.
If you let him sing,
everybody's gonna hear it
and viciously rip on him
for the rest of his life.
Aw, man, what am I gonna do?
The elevator!
Right, we'll push him
down the elevator shaft.
I'll do it.
We're not gonna push
the hottest guy in Seattle
down an elevator shaft.
You said the elevator...
I meant
when he gets in the elevator
to come up here,
we kill the power
so he can't get out.
Then he'll be stuck
there while we do the show.
Ah! Okay.
He'll think it's an accident,
I won't have to tell him
he's a lame singer,
and nobody's feelings get hurt.
Can't we lock him
in the elevator
and hurt his feelings?
♪
Yo, Jake.
Show starts in 15 minutes.
Yeah,
you better get on up there.
Awesome. Let's do it.
Whoa, whoa!
Where you going there, partner?
Just going up to do the show.
Well, don't take the stairs.
You don't wanna get all sweaty
in your fancy singing shirt.
No.
Right.
I'll take the elevator.
Yes.
There you go.
Do that.
Enjoy elevating.
You guys aren't coming?
We'll be up in a few minutes.
After we...
Uh... blow our noses.
Yeah.
Can't do a web show
with a nose full of goo.
Where's the breaker panel?
Behind the robot painting.
Which one's for the elevator?
The red one.
There.
Hey, what happened?
Uh, I think the elevator
got stuck again!
Yeah, it's not moving!
Well, don't worry!
We'll get you out of there!
Eventually!
I got it.
Hello?
♪
Hey.
Hi.
Is Jake trapped?
Like a monkey in a box.
Why would a monkey be in a box?
What am I? A monkey expert?
You just said...
How much time
'til the show starts?
Nine minutes, 20 seconds.
Okay, when it gets
to the part where Jake
was supposed to sing,
we'll just improvise
and talk about something funny.
Like Freddie's haircut.
I heard that.
You were supposed to.
Okay, when the show starts,
put the camera on me,
and Sam will come out when...
Hey!
I got the door up!
Hang on.
I'm out.
Awesome.
Yay.
We thought you'd be
stuck in there for a while.
Me, too.
But I found this little
emergency trap door
at the top of the elevator,
climbed up,
squeezed myself through it,
and here I am.
There you are.
Yay.
So now you can be on the show.
Yeah, good thing.
I don't wanna disappoint
my grandmother.
Your grandmother?
Yeah.
She's never heard me
sing before,
so when I told her
I was gonna be on your show,
she went out,
bought her very first computer.
Aww.
Yeah.
She'd been saving up
for a new foot,
but watching me sing
was more important to her.
Your grandmother only
has one foot?
Uh-huh.
What happened to the other one?
She had this cat,
forgot to feed him.
I don't really like
to talk about it.
We go live in six minutes.
Ooh, I better get set.
Okay, we're gonna go check
the lighting in the hallway.
Who cares about the lighting
in the...
We can't let Jake
sing on the show!
You want him to disappoint
Grammy One Foot?
You want him to be humiliated
in front of the whole world?
The boy can't sing.
So?
Half the pop stars
on the charts can't sing.
They fix their voices
with computers or something.
Yeah.
Too bad we don't know
a computer geek
that'll do anything you ask.
No.
Can you fix his voice or not?
Yes.
But I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not gonna help turn
"Mr. Awesome"
into "Mr. Totally Awesome."
Please?
No.
If I do, will you kiss me?
No!
Then no.
Oh, come on!
I'm gonna puke
all over both of you.
Freddie.
Just one little kiss
on the lips.
No.
Cheek?
Nose?
No.
Okay, fine I'll do it.
Thank you.
Let's go.
And now...
On iCarly...
We're gonna do something
a little special.
Carly and I are gonna start
punching each other in the face.
The one with the last
tooth wins.
We're just kidding.
What we are gonna do
is our first ever
live music performance on
iCarly.
Yeah, we are.
So sit back,
keep your hands off that mouse.
Or track pad.
And get excited
for our special guest,
Jake Krandle.
How you guys doing?
This is a song called
"Whatever My Love,"
and I'd like to dedicate this
to my grandmother.
Keep on hopping, Grandma.
♪
Get ready, he's about to sing.
I got him.
♪ You're so beautiful ♪
♪ I need the world to see ♪
♪ You're my miracle ♪
♪ Just take the time
that you need ♪
Is it working?
♪ To breathe ♪
♪ And never
mind the things I've done ♪
♪ You make me feel like
I'm the rising sun ♪
Aw. Pretty.
♪ You bathe me in your light ♪
I'm kind of thirsty.
♪ And show me it's alright ♪
Where is my punch?
What flavour punch did I buy?
♪ And you'll always be ♪
Give me that nose.
♪ You'll always be the one ♪
Yes! Yes!
That's my grandson!
That's my Jakey! Yes! Yes!
♪
Ugh, I hate mornings.
Why can't school start at,
like, 2:00 in the afternoon?
And end at 2:04?
Yes.
Someone who understands.
Uh-oh.
That's Jake's ex-girlfriend.
Why is he kissing
his ex-girlfriend?
You don't kiss your
ex-girlfriend.
That's the whole point
of the "ex!"
Sorry, kiddo.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
You want backup?
I'm good.
Hey.
Oh, hey, Carly.
Hey, Jake.
You sang so awesome.
Call me.
Or me.
Nice.
I know.
I've been getting that
all morning.
Yeah, you've been having
all kinds of fun this morning.
What do you mean?
Well, when I walked in,
I kind of noticed you
and Stephanie.
Oh. You saw that?
Yeah.
Listen, I really thought
we'd broken up for good.
But she saw me sing
on your web show,
and then she called to tell me
how great she thought I was,
and looks like we're
kind of back together now.
Oh. Awesome.
Yeah, but I guess things
happen for a reason, right?
I'm back with Steph,
and now I don't feel weird about
getting between you and Freddie.
Me and Freddie?
Freddie and I aren't dating!
Come on.
I saw you kiss his nose.
Well, yeah,
but we're not dating.
Let's all get to class.
I'll see you around.
But it was just a nose kiss!
Aw, come on!
It was strictly nasal!
Hi, Carly.
Hi, Sam.
I love iCarly.
Okay, okay, check out
what I can do with my eyes.
♪
Mmm!